rangercentral.com 2007-06-30

# Power Rangers Central - Privacy Statement

### 

RANGERCENTRAL.COM has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and spreading practices for this Web site: RANGERCENTRAL.COM

  Personal Information  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

What do you do with the information collected?  
All information collected will be used solely by Power Rangers Central and not given, sold, or otherwise transferred to third parties in a personally identifiable form.  
  
Use of Cookies  
Power Rangers Central may make use of cookies (small pieces of information placed on your computer by our website) for information collection purposes. Any information provided by these cookies will not be personally identifiable and is solely used to improve your experience at our site. We dot not passively connect personally identifiable information through the use of cookies.  
   
External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. RANGERCENTRAL.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

 Third Party Advertising  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, feel free to contact us at 

[webmaster@rangercentral.com](mailto:webmaster@rangercentral.com?subject=To%20Webmaster%20of%20PRC).
